Reuben Kadish
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1934-1993, undated, Series 8:; (boxes 5-7, 67 folders)
  - Exhibition announcements and catalogs for others, 1960-1989, undated, (9 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5660)
  - Exhibition announcements and catalogs for others, 1990-1992, (5 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Reproductions of artwork by Kadish, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Reproductions of artwork by others, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Press releases, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Programs, 1978-1990 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Program, Dodgers baseball program autographed by Darryl Strawberry, 1991 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Catalogs for the loan of artworks, 1960-1988 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Catalogs for schools, 1957-1971 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Catalogs for art supplies, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Catalogs for miscellaneous equipment, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Miscellaneous catalogs, 1983, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Travel brochures for the U.S., 1989, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Travel brochures for other countries, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Picture postcards, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1968, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
- Photographs, 1913-1992, undated, Series 9:; (boxes 7-9, sol 10, 46 folders)
  This series includes eight photographs donated to the Archives of American Art by Kadish in 1984 dating from 1934-1965. One photograph is of Kadish, Philip Guston (whose name was changed from Philip Goldstein in 1935), Jules Langsner, and Alfaro Siqueiros working on a mural in Morelia, Mexico. Another photograph shows Kadish and Guston posed with their mural for the Library of the City of Hope, Duarte, California. Other photographs are of friends including Mrs. Fletcher Martin, and of the wedding of Kadish's son, Dan, to Guston's daughter, Musa.
  Other photographs included in the collection are of Kadish, his family, friends, and colleagues. Photographs of Kadish with friends and colleagues include Jules Langsner, David Alfaro Siqueiros, nine photographs of Philip Guston, two photographs of Jackson Pollock, and three photographs of Willem De Kooning. There are also photographs of Kadish's studio, farm, gallery installations, and artwork, including several WPA murals.
  Miscellaneous photographs of Kadish with family include one photograph with Leonard Stark. Family wedding photographs include four photographs of Philip Guston. Travel photographs include views of Siam, India, ancient stone monuments in Great Britain, and Barbara Hepworth's studio in Cornwall. Photographs of miscellaneous murals by Kadish include a photograph of a mural destroyed by Los Angeles police raid by “Red” Hynes, and two photographs of a mural, possibly by Luis Arenal.
  Forty-four transparencies of miscellaneous sculpture by Kadish, 1976-1992, have not been microfilmed. See also sol 10 for photographs of Kadish and his family, friends, and studio.
  - Kadish, 1913-1987, (5 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Kadish with family, miscellaneous, 1913-1990 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Kadish with family, wedding of Dan Kadish and Musa Guston, 1962 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Kadish with family, Ruth and Morris [Moishe] Kadish's trip to Chile (see also sol 10), undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Kadish with friends and colleagues (see also sol 10), 1933-1982, undated, (7 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Studio (see also sol 10), 1983, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Farm, 1955, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Four unidentified gallery installations, undated, (4 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, works on paper, undated (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, work on Siquieros mural Triumph of Good Over Evil at University in Morelia, Mexico, (including photographs of Siquieros, Kadish, Philip Goldstein (Guston), and Jules Langsner), 1933 (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, WPA mural Physical Growth of Man at the City of Hope TB Sanitarium, Duarte, California, by Kadish and Philip Goldstein (Guston), circa 1936, (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, WPA mural A Dissertation on Alchemy at the San Francisco State College Science Hall, executed between Dec, 1936 and Aug, 1937, assisted by Urban Neininger, undated, (3 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, miscellaneous murals, 1930-1934, undated (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, miscellaneous sculpture, undated (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by Kadish, transparencies, 1976-1992 (Box 8 (hol), Reel unfilmed)
  - Artwork by others, monoprints by Scott Carpenter, undated (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Artwork by others, miscellaneous, undated (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Travel photographs, 1991-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Duplicate photographs, (4 folders) (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Miscellaneous negatives, [1970s] (Box 8 (hol), Reel 5660)
  - Miscellaneous negatives, [1970s], undated, (2 folders) (Box 9 (pam), Reel 5660)
- Artifacts, undated, Series 10:; (box 9, 1 folder)
  Artifacts consist of tw cross sections of vertebrae.
  - Bones: 2 sections of vertebrae, undated (Box 9 (pam), Reel unfilmed)